http://www.soundcedar.com/info/about-us/privacy-policy/

info here
close
Naturally Beautiful
ABOUT US  About Sound Cedar  Contact Us  Photo Gallery  Social Media  Delivery Service  Shipping Service  Our Website  LEED Certification SPECIES  Cedar  Douglas Fir  Hemlock  Treated  Mahogany  IPE  Exotic Hardwoods  Get Current Prices SIDING  Cedar Siding  Siding Choices  Siding Videos  Cement Siding vs Cedar Siding  Siding Materials Calculator  Prices for Siding  Clear Veneer Siding DECKING  Decking Choices  Deckorators Decking  Decking Installation Tips  Finishing Your Deck  Decking Materials Calculator  Prices for Decking TIMBERS  Timbers and Beams  Timber Sizes  Timber Price Quote  Prices on Timbers  Timber Structures  Timber and Beam Ideas FENCING  Cedar Fencing  Fence Posts  Cedar Split Rail  Fencing Materials Calculator  Prices for Cedar Fencing TRIM  Cedar Trim Boards  Finger Joint Trim Boards  Pre Primed Trim Boards SAUNAS  Saunas HARDWARE  Hardware
Lumber > About Us > Our Website > Privacy PolicySHAREOur WebsitePrivacy PolicyThis privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for soundcedar.com. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Opt OutYou may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the contact form or phone number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
SecurityWe take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
We never ask to collect sensitive information (such as credit card data) through our website.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
CookiesWe use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site. LinksThis web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information. UpdatesOur Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 360-424-4548 or via email through our contact form.
Download this page as PDFAsk about PricesNEXT: Photo Gallery
